Okay...
Sakamoto's finally cornered Oda.
He has three chips.
Oda has four chips.
Whoever wins this will have a complete set.
Finally...
Finally, the first player to beat the game.
S-Sakamoto's been defeated?
What the hell happened?
Oda was still holding the remote.
When he threw down his trunk and BIMs,
he hid it in his sleeve.
In other words, Oda lured him into a trap he'd set in advance.
Amazing.
He's unbelievable!
Now Oda's got a full set.
No, wait.
The one who fell for the trap...
was Oda!
No way!
H-How?
Because you were watching the monitor from Oda's viewpoint.
Sakamoto never approached the trunk.
He just made it look like he had.
Oda could only see from the left,
so he couldn't rely on depth perception.
Sakamoto had the better plan!
Now both know the other survived and where they are.
It's not over yet!
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
This is where tomorrow brings a new game
It's time to learn that pain is gain
Ready fight
To squash my past despair
kako no shitsubou nuritsubusu tame ni
I've had to sacrifice my future
gisei ni shite kita mirai
Until my life expires
boku no life ga tsukiru made
I'll keep fighting my fate
sono sadame buchikowashiteiku no sa
Ah, break out and start a revolution
Searching for the exact answer
hitotsu no kotae wo sagashite
I challenge myself to an extreme race
genkai no race ni idonde
I know it's my only chance
ichidokiri no chansu to shitte
I'll overcome my preordained fate
seotta unmei koeteikun da yo
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
the game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
I knew it was a trap.
He'll sneak through the smoke to grab his BIMs.
If I die, I'm taking you with me!
Sakamoto's striking back!
Now it's Oda who's being hunted!
What?
No way.
I left this BIM because a dead man was holding it.
Seems I'll need it now.
Now, it's my turn.
He's running away?
Loser.
If you don't have the guts to kill, you can't beat me!
He saw my attack coming?
That guy...
High Level
Who is he?
Another explosion.
R-Ryouta!
You can't just rush out there.
A second ago, the radar showed several people.
You could be attacked.
Your own life comes before all else.
If you aren't careful, you'll end up in hell...
in a heartbeat.
Ryouta?
Are you Ryouta?
Who are you?
How did you know my name?
I knew it.
Well, I guess it doesn't matter either way.
W-Wait up.
Who are you?!
Who is he?
How did he know who I am?
Damn it!
This doesn't make any sense.
Nice job, Sakamoto!
That really excited me.
What an amazing battle.
You rarely see a fight like that, even among the world's best players.
You're...
that kid!
I want to have a battle like that.
That's why... I'll be taking this.
Y-You...
Your belt fell off in that explosion.
I just picked it up.
Damn.
What's wrong?
These were mine to begin with.
And you can't use them until I'm dead, right?
See ya, Sakamoto!
In the end, I never did get the food.
I lost those BIMs, too.
I have no strength left for anything.
Ryouta!
Sakamoto!
Himiko... Mr. Date.
Are you okay, Sakamoto?
Yeah, but I lost the trunk.
It's fine.
I'm just glad you're alive.
I'm sorry.
You useless brat!
Thanks for looking for me,
Himiko.
H-Himiko?
Come on...
I'm soaked.
And I haven't had a bath.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
Let's head back.
What the hell?
The heat melted the plastic...
and it stinks.
Gross.
After all that, the food you brought is ruined!
I don't know how you can eat this crap.
If you don't want it, you don't have to eat it, Heademi.
Learn my name, already.
My name is...
Hidemi.
Kinoshita Hidemi.
What's wrong with "Heademi"?
It isn't my name...
And what are you looking at?
Eat your food, Heady.
That's not my name, either!
Don't get mad.
We're partners, right?
Right?
That man... How does he know me?
I recognized his voice.
Actually, he looks like...
him.
Hey, Ryouta.
Oda Nobutaka.
He was the kind of guy who excelled at everything.
Oda
Nobutaka
He always had the best grades.
Oda
Nobutaka
He was good at sports.
He was nice to everyone,
had tons of friends...
The girls liked him, too.
Anything he did, he was great at.
When I was little, I wanted to be like that.
But I couldn't beat him at anything.
It got to the point where it gave me a complex.
For some reason, he talked to me a lot.
Maybe because we both had single mothers.
Anyway, we would often hang out.
He was fun to be with.
I thought I was the only one he was really open with.
So, I was open with him.
You like Aiko?
D-Don't tell anyone, okay?
I opened up to him.
Well? Did you ask her out?
Like I could.
Serizawa Aiko, huh?
She's kinda plain, but pretty cute, huh?
Why don't you ask her out?
I'm fine with things as they are.
I can't just walk up to girls and ask them out like you.
Idiot.
You're gonna die a virgin.
Seems to me like you're satisfied with holding yourself back.
To me, you're like a gullible little kid.
The first one to move wins.
Stay on the defensive, and you'll lose your chance.
Ryouta, that is the only difference between us,
regardless of whether you can understand that.
Buzz off.
I thought that only self-confident people could say that.
And he was, so he acted in kind.
A-Aiko...
What's wrong, Aiko?
What happened?
What are you doing, Nobutaka?
Weren't you dating me?!
Shut your mouth.
Hey!
Don't walk away from me, Nobutaka!
What happened?
I feel bad about it.
I asked you what happened!
I did it with Aiko.
Wha...
What are you talking about?
Aiko came and said she liked me.
What's it to you?
Not like you—
I...
I was betrayed.
Humiliated.
I'd opened my heart to him.
He humiliated me!
Next thing I knew, I was surrounded by a bunch of people.
We were both suspended.
He quit school.
I heard he became a host.
Even ended up with his own club.
But none of that matters.
Why did he do something like that?
If I'd at least asked him that,
would it have satisfied me a bit?
The first one to move wins.
Are you Ryouta?
So that really was Oda.
Knowing him,
any number of people might have wanted him sent to this island.
But is he...
Is he going to be my enemy?
That looks good.
It's a makeshift curry gruel.
I can't wait to have some.
We have to let it steep a little more.
Damn it.
He didn't get the food and ended up running away like a coward.
And now, I have to share the little bit of food I have left?
I don't know why I even joined them!
Mr. Date?
I'm glad you found a trunk.
We appreciate the food.
Yeah.
That first day, I was fortunate to get some.
There isn't much left, but it should at least last another day.
But tomorrow, we have to get more.
Another carrier will come tomorrow?
Oh, uh...
If I know too much, they'll get suspicious.
Well, you see...
Since I got some the first day, and I'm a bit cowardly,
I spent a lot of time thinking about the food.
I heard that engine sound every day, at noon.
So I'm sure there'll be a plane tomorrow, too.
I get it. That's amazing.
This'll make it a lot easier to get the food.
It's ready.
Mr. Taira, please have some.
There isn't a lot, but I let it steep a long time.
It doesn't have much flavor, but it'll fill you up.
Thank you...
but I'm not hungry.
That's no good. You need to build up your strength to get better.
Come on, just a little.
May I?
This is bad.
The lizard's venom is keeping his wound from healing.
We need some serum immediately.
He requires proper treatment,
or he'll die.
But there's no way...
Ryouta.
Can I have a word?
What is it?
We're...
Just come with me.
I'll make sure he eats.
Go on.
Thanks.
What's the problem, Himiko?
Go back to that abandoned building?
Yes.
Ms. Murasaki said there was a medicine supply.
I'm sure we can find something there.
I see.
Whoever used that building before kept some in case of lizard bites.
They should have some serum.
And Mr. Date is a doctor.
He should know what medicine we need.
You're taking him with you?
Of course.
Couldn't we ask Ms. Murasaki to give it to us?
He's actually examined Mr. Taira,
so it'd be better if he got it.
But...
Now, chew it slowly.
Yes, like that.
Slowly, slowly...
Damn it!
I'm wasting valuable food on a man who's almost dead.
There's no point in working with them anymore.
I think it's time to say goodbye.
Open your mouth.
Yes, slowly.
You're doing great.
Mr. Date.
Yes?
We know where there might be medicine.
Could you come with us?
There's medicine here?
I don't know if there's anything we can use to help Mr. Taira.
But let's go take a look.
S-Sakamoto...
You're going to leave me again?
I'll be back as soon as I can.
You really hate Mr. Date that much?
I just don't trust him.
There's something off about him.
Really?
He seems like such a good person. It's hard to imagine him being sent here.
He just acts that way.
He's not really like that.
Like what happened before.
He tried to kill me with that girl.
But he made it sound like he saved me.
I can't trust him.
And you, Ryouta...
You told him we have three chips!
I'm sure he plans to...
Hey, Himiko.
If we're going to survive on this island,
I think it's important to trust people.
And if you don't start by trusting them, they won't ever really trust you.
We know he didn't use a single BIM until he met us.
And he shared valuable food with us.
I believe in him.
That's enough.
I won't bring it up again.
W-Wait...
Sakamoto, are we there yet?
Almost.
This is an old building.
And it's big, too.
I'm amazed you found a medicine supply here.
Do you know where it is?
I don't know.
I was going to ask Ms. Murasaki.
Oh.
We should keep the fact that she lives here a secret, right?
Of course!
Is something wrong?
N-No.
It sounds like she doesn't know exactly where it is.
We'll look for it.
You don't know where it is?
Then how do you know it's here?
Um, that's...
Crap.
L-Last time, I got lost in here.
I don't remember which way I went.
I get lost easily.
That's right.
She's kind of dim.
I didn't say that!
Okay.
Then it would be better to split up and search.
Then I'll take the second floor.
I'll check the annex.
Send two radar pings if you find it.
Understood.
I'm back here?
Nothing has changed in six months.
These maze-like hallways...
little windows to toss bombs through.
It's almost like the ones in charge wanted us to fight here.
The bastards!
The medicine here won't do anyone any good.
Most of it's long past its expiration date.
There's no way I can find a usable serum here either.
But it doesn't matter.
I'll just toss in some bottles. That'll be enough.
Mr. Date?
You've already found it?
Yes, I stocked up on some tools and medicines I can use.
Thank you very much.
Sakamoto, do you doubt me?
I overheard your conversation with that girl.
Just so we're clear,
you can't survive here without mutual trust.
I want to believe in you guys.
And I want you to believe in me.
I... understand.
I'm sorry.
Okay, hold on to this on the way back.
R-Right.
It has important materials inside.
Be careful with it.
I-I will.
Wh-Why's he...
so intimidating?
To me, you're like a gullible little kid.
I'm sure he plans to...
Now, let's hurry.
We have to call Himiko, first.
Ah. We do, don't we?
Why is she running?
Ryouta!
Oh, Himiko.
We found the medicine.
Ryouta, get rid of the trunk!
Hurry! Throw it away!
That woman...
Wh-Why?
Just do it!
The trunk's got a BIM...
There's a bomb inside it!
Wh-What?!
Die.
Ryouta!
I hold my breath and close my eyes
iki wo sezu me wo fuseta
The sky is glittering so brightly
hikyou na hodo kirameku aozora ga
Coloring the space over our heads
kono machi no zujou wo color
I can't stop shedding tears
tomedonaku namida furaseru kara
I can't just push it aside as memories
omoide ni wa dekinai
Just seeing you made me so happy
au dake de ureshikatta
I didn't understand you
kimi no koto shirazu ni
And hurt you
kizutsukete
Nobody knows
nobody knows
You don't have to give me another chance
gomen ne watashi wo mou
Just forget about me
yurusanaide wasurete
He's dead!
Now it's just the stupid schoolgirl and the dying cripple.
I'll get all the chips I need again!
The one to survive will be me, Date Masahito.
Episode
Revival